akashbca205@gmail.com

Redhills, Chennai-600052



EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Creative Graphic Designer experience in branding, marketing, and print design. Impressive track record delivering print design, brand identity, and web design projects within the time, cost, and quality constraints. Brings a keen eye for detail with expertise in Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Classroom co-ordinator Shankar IAS Academy Anna nagar,chennai Mar 2024 - Oct 2024

- Co ordinator Logistics and operations for shankar ias academy.
- Managed a classroom material, attendance and students queries.
- Provided a technical support faculty and students via phone, email and in person.
- Uploaded a video lectures study material to cloud based platform (eg..youtube, google drive).
- Coordinating with faculty to record a video and edit to upload a lectures.

Process Associated DATA MART PVT LTD Ambattur, chennai

Nov 2023- Mar 2024

- Managed and process a shipping documentations of fedex express.
- Process and verified a shipping documents (airways bills and invoice etc).
- Co-ordinate with logistics teams and resolved a delivery issues.
- To work on data entry and Management in fedex company.

Graphic Designer Sri Venkateswaraa Medcity Hospital & Research Institue

Oct 2024 Present

- Designed logos, brochures, business cards, and other marketing materials for Sri Venkateswaraa Medcity and Sri Venkateswaraa University industries.
- Developed and implemented effective design concepts that aligned with Sri Venkateswaraa Medcity and Sri Venkateswaraa University brand identities.
- Ensured timely delivery of designs and revisions, meeting project deadlines and expectations.
- Collaborated with the design team to brainstorm innovative ideas and approaches.
- Good knowledge in DTP Operator.

EDUCATION

Madras University

Sri Devi Arts and Science College Bachelor of Computer Application 2020 – 2023

SKILLS

Proficient in Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word)

Experienced in video editing and graphics designing using ,figma,adobe illustrator,canva and camteshiya .

Strong knowledge of HTML and CSS

Familiarity with web development principles

PROJECT

Title: ONLINE FOOD ORDERING WEBSITE Link: https://github.com/AKASHM205

Duration: 3 Months

Description: Developed an Online food ordering system, a crucial feature for websites, enabling customers to select and manage items for ordering conveniently. Additionally, it offers a "save for later" feature, enhancing the ordering experience.

Hardware Requirement: Q uad-coreP rocessor, 8 G BR AM

Software Requirement : Database : My SQL

Web Browser: Google Chrome, IE, BROWSER

CERTIFICATIONS

I have completed by CORE JAVA, SQL DATABASE, DATA ANALYST course from anudip foundation.

I have completed PYTHON, HTML Course from Sololearn. Link: https://api2.sololearn.com/v2/certificates/CCVAT3KQBQ/CCYFJ3UKXL / image/png

I have completed UI/UX design live workshop from Just Rise Technologies Pvt Ltd.

I have successfully completed the PERSONALITY DEVELOPMENT and PLACEMENT TRAINING course conducted by ACTION DNA.